Guide to the Judy Malloy Papers, 1956-2010
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Personal Materials, (4 boxes)
  - Ethel Hazen Lillard and Walter Huston Lillard (Box 16)
    Photos and mementos of Malloy's maternal grandparents. Ethel was a graduate of Smith College; Walter ("Cappy") studied at Dartmouth and Oxford, was headmaster of Tabor Academy for many yars, and served in Vienna under the United Nations as Chief of the Resettlement Division of the International Refugee Organization in 1946 and 1947.
  - Walter Huston Lillard Writings (Box 16)
    Most of the material is drawn from Memorable Men of My Time (whose trails I have crossed), the original manuscript of which is available at Dartmouth's Rauner Special Collections Library. Selections cover Theodore Roosevelt, Franklin Delano Roosevelt, King Leopold II of Belgium, and Sir Winston Churchill, among many others, as well as various other narratives and an article on the Dartmouth football team. Folder includes Lillard's business card from the United Nations.
  - Sean Malloy (Box 16)
    Materials relating to Malloy's son, including photos, mementos from his wedding, educational and professional documents (he earned a BA from UC Berkeley and a PhD in history from Stanford), a photocopy of one of his academic articles, and documents from his time as Assistant Editor of HotWired.
  - Frederic C. and Jane Lillard Bartter (Box 17)
    Materials relating to Malloy's uncle and aunt, with whom she lived while working at the Library of Congress. Includes photos with various other relatives and biographical materials/obituaries for Frederic.
  - Evan and Virginia Collins (Box 17)
    Materials relating to Malloy's uncle and aunt, including photos and an obituary for Evan.
  - Willie Loco Alexander and the confessions, Autre Chose, 1982 (LP) (Box 23)
    Walter Powers, second from left on cover, was a member of the Boston-based group.
  - Winchester High School Yearbook, Aberjona 1960 (Box 17)
  - Judy Malloy (Powers) Diplomas (Box 17)
    Winchester High School, 1960; Middlebury College, 1964
  - Middlebury College Mementos, 1960-1964 and later (undated) (Box 17)
    Includes yearbook pictures and cards/letters from Middlebury friends.
  - Family friends, undated (Box 17)
  - Calendars, 1976-1990 (noninclusive) (Box 17)
    1976, 1977, 1981, 1984, 1990
  - Library Work, 1964-1977 and undated (Box 17)
    Materials relating to Malloy's various library positions, including contractor work for the Goddard Space Center's automated catalog, Special Services Libraries in Germany, and the Library of Congress, among others.
  - Documents, 1956-1969 (Box 17)
    Includes horsemanship certificate from the Chimney Corners Camp; National Rifle Association Junior Diploma; and certificate of completion from the University of Denver Graduate School of Librarianship Library Systems Analysis and Design Institute.
  - Web stats for Malloy's page on The WELL, January and March 2006 (Box 17)
  - Sayward Farnum, The Five by Five: A History of the 555th Antiaircraft Artillery Automatic Weapons Battalion (Mobile), 1946 (Box 17)
    This unit was with Malloy's father's unit at Camp Hulen, TX; the book is inscribed to her father.
  - Henry David Thoreau, Cape Cod (Box 17)
    Includes Cohasset, where Malloy's maternal grandparents lived and Malloy and her mother lived while her father was overseas, and Wellfleet, where the family spent some summers.
  - Music/events influential on Malloy's work; contact with catalogers at UCLA (Box 25)
  - Lament of Roslindale, music written by Malloy's brother (Box 25)
  - Paint box, undated (Box 26)
    Belonged to Malloy's grandmother. Malloy writes, "the odds and ends in the box are from different sources. The fan and pieces of cloth were given to me by Toshiba because they used my image in an early laptop commercial."
  - Longest Day VHS box (Box 26)
    Kept by Malloy since her father was a Normandy veteran.